Hanung Addi Chandra Utomo

+6282134950080 - hanungutomo45@gmail.com



WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2024 - present

Al Engineer

PT Global Data Inspirasi

Explore and finetuning deep learning model for NLP Task and Computer Vision

- Developing Database Integrated LLMs Chatbot using Agents with Ilama index and Open Webui
- Finetuning T5 LLM model for aspect based sentiment analysis Finetuning BERT LLM Model for multi-label classification task
- Finetuning YOLOv8, YOLOv9, and YOLOv10 for object detection task and classification task
- Creating Pipeline for object detection using cv2 and Supervision Roboflow like
 Dwelling Time, Object Counting, and Object Tracking
- Develop an REST API for model inference using Flask REST API, for image or text tasks.
- Model deployment with Docker Container

Mentoring Internship to work on some projects:

- Object Detection Models
- Chatbot
- CV Analyzer

Aug 2023 - Jan 2024

Data Engineer

PT Global Data Inspirasi

- Developing ETL system
- Managing Databases like PostgreSQL & Elasticsearch
- Monitor and Developing Crawler using APIs and Selenium
- Deploy and Managing Crawler and Scheduler like Airflow using Docker

May 2021 - Apr 2022

Data Engineer

PT Global Data Inspirasi

It started with an Internship as Data Engineer. in datains i was learning basic data scrapping, basic database (SQL & NoSQL), Basic APIs (Flask using python) and basic IT Automation.

EDUCATION

Jul 2019 - present

Internet Engineering Technology (Teknologi Rekayasa Internet)

Universitas Gadjah Mada (Gadjah Mada University)

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022

Machine Learning Path

Bangkit Academy 2022

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Undergraduated Student from Gadjah Mada University, Majoring at Network Engineering Technology. Having an interest at Machine Learning and Data Engineering. I am a TensorFlow Developer Certified and Bangkit Academy 2022 - Machine Learning Path Graduate. Having an experience mainly using Python Programming Language that i used for developing ML Projects such as Chatbots, Computer Vision projects, and simple Classification models..

SKILLS

- LLMs (Groq, Ollama, Huggingface, ect)
- Computer Vision (YOLO, Ultralytics, OpenCV)
- Deep Learning (Pytorch, Tensorflow)
- Databases (PostgreSQL, MySQL, Elasticsearch)
- HTML/CSS/Javascript
- REST APIs (Python)
- Python

SEMINARS AND TRAININGS

Feb 2022 - Feb 2022

Bangkit Academy 2022 - Machine Learning Path

Google, GoTo, Traveloka

PROJECTS

May 2024 - Jun 2024

Vehicle Counting Computer Vision

Machine Learning Engineer

- Finetuning yolov8, yolov9 and yolov10 for detection 5 classes (pedestrian, car, truck, motorcycle, bus), and compare them by performance and efficiency
- Creating a working pipeline to process video and gather or detect data for counting vehicle
- Using line on 4 lanes as a tools for counting whether vehicle is out or in
- Explore SAHI method (Slicing image before inferencing, ans then merging results) for inproving model performance

Feb 2024 - Apr 2024

Dwelling Time Computer Vision

Machine Learning Engineer

- Using Yolov8 Computer Vision Model
- Creating custom inference pipeline for detect and tracking person object
- Creating function to count total detected frame/fps as time for counting dwelling time
- Creating a section box, whether to counting serviced time or waiting time

Jan 2024 - Mar 2024

Aspect Based Sentiment Analysis

Machine Learning Engineer

 Finetuning model t5 instruct model for extracting aspect or topic on Hotel Review data using transformers and torch

May 2022 - Jun 2022

NutrieCARE - Capstone Project Bangkit Academy

Machine Learning Engineer

CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

Jul 2022 **TensorFlow Developer Certification**

Tensorflow

Apr 2022 DeepLearning.Al TensorFlow Developer Specialization

Coursera

Mar 2022 Google IT Automation with Python Specialization

Coursera

Mar 2022 Google IT Automation Certificate

Coursera

Mar 2022 Mathematics for Machine Learning Specialization

Coursera